Guide to the Mix Collection, 1970-2014 (Bulk 1987-2001) MSS.143
Fales Library and Special Collections
- SERIES XIX: Miscellaneous, 116345
  - Subseries H: Jack Waters/Allied Productions/Naked Eye Cinema, 116535
    - Jack Waters - Grants/fundraising - The Pollock-Krasner Foundation, 1990; 116565 (Box 34, Folder 1656)
    - Allied Productions - Expenses - Activity report for Winter and Spring newsletters, 1992; 116564 (Box 34, Folder 1657)
    - Allied Productions - Expenses - MCI card, 1991; 116563 (Box 34, Folder 1658)
    - Allied Productions - Expenses - Telephone bill, 1991; 116562 (Box 34, Folder 1659)
    - Allied Productions - Statements - Call for contributions, 1991; 116561 (Box 34, Folder 1660)
    - Allied Productions - Statements - Call for submissions (Flique), 1992; 116560 (Box 34, Folder 1661)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - Department of Cultural Affairs contract, 1991; 116559 (Box 34, Folder 1662)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - Department of Cultural Affairs contract and final report figures, 1991; 116558 (Box 34, Folder 1663)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - Grants pending, 1989, 116557 (Box 34, Folder 1664)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - National Endowment for the Arts, 1984-1985; 116556 (Box 34, Folder 1665)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - National Endowment for the Arts - application and final report, 1988-1989; 116555 (Box 34, Folder 1666)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - National Endowment for the Arts - InterArts application and final report + New York Foundation of the Arts Artist Fellowship guidelines, 1986-1989; 116554 (Box 35, Folder 1667)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - National Endowment for the Arts - InterArts grant application, 1989; 116553 (Box 35, Folder 1668)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - National Endowment for the Arts - InterArts grant application, 1990/1991; 116552 (Box 35, Folder 1669)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - National Endowment for the Arts - dance project application, 1988-1991; 116551 (Box 35, Folder 1670)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - National Endowment for the Arts - grant application, 1991/1992; 116550 (Box 35, Folder 1671)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - ABC No Rio final report, 1989/1990; 116549 (Box 35, Folder 1672)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - ABC No Rio final report, 1990; 116548 (Box 35, Folder 1673)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - ABC No Rio grant application, 1989; 116547 (Box 35, Folder 1674)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - correspondence re: Antiutopia, 1988-1989; 116546 (Box 35, Folder 1675)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - cultural services contract, 1990; 116545 (Box 35, Folder 1676)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - final report form, 1989/1990; 116544 (Box 35, Folder 1677)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - final report form for ABC No Rio repairs, 1990; 116543 (Box 35, Folder 1678)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - final report form and cultural services contract, 1990/1991; 116542 (Box 35, Folder 1679)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - grant application, 1989; 116541 (Box 35, Folder 1680)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - project descriptions, 1989; 116540 (Box 35, Folder 1681)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - miscellaneous administrative files, 1989; 116539 (Box 35, Folder 1682)
    - Naked Eye Cinema - Carl George correspondence to filmmakers, 1987; 116538 (Box 35, Folder 1683)
    - Naked Eye Cinema - Call for queer films, n.d.; 116537 (Box 35, Folder 1684)
    - Naked Eye Cinema - Catalog, 1987; 116536 (Box 35, Folder 1685)
  - Subseries I: Anthology Film Archives, 116531
    - Correspondence and other info re: gay filmmakers (Gregory Markopoulos, Stefan Hayn), 1993-1995; 116534 (Box 35, Folder 1686)
    - February 1994 ticket sales figures, 116533 (Box 35, Folder 1687)
    - Miscellany, n.d.; 116532 (Box 35, Folder 1688)
  - Subseries J: Miscellaneous/Undated Files (see also Oversize series), 116524
    - Business cards and menus, ?-1997; 116530 (Box 35, Folder 1689)
    - G.L. Towers Syndicates Reinsurance form, `989; 116529 (Box 35, Folder 1691)
    - Notice for available office space, 1996; 116528 (Box 35, Folder 1692)
    - Queer film bibliography, n.d.; 116527 (Box 35, Folder 1693)
    - Unknown correspondence, 116526 (Box 35, Folder 1694)
    - Miscellany, n.d.; 116525 (Box 35, Folder 1695)
  - Subseries K: Books, 116510
    - Arendt, Hannah, On violence, 1970; 116523 (Box 36, Folder 1696)
    - Bergman, David, Gaiety transfigured, 1991; 116522 (Box 36, Folder 1697)
    - Dollimore, Jonathan, Sexual dissidence: Augustine to Wilde, Freud to Foucault, 1991; 116521 (Box 36, Folder 1698)
    - Goldberg, Natalie, Writing down the bones: freeing the writer within, 1986; 116520 (Box 36, Folder 1699)
    - Kaufman, Lloyd, Sight and mind, 1974; 116519 (Box 36, Folder 1700)
    - Langford, Michael, The darkroom handbook, 1984; 116518 (Box 36, Folder 1701)
    - Lorde, Audre, Chosen poems: old and new, 1982; 116517 (Box 36, Folder 1702)
    - Milberg, Doris, Repeat performances: a guide to Hollywood movie remakes, 1990; 116516 (Box 36, Folder 1703)
    - National Campaign for Freedom of Expression, NCFE handbook to understanding, preparing for, and responding to challenges to your freedom of artistic expression, 1998; 116515 (Box 36, Folder 1704)
    - Phillips, Julia, You'll never eat lunch in this town again, 1991; 116514 (Box 36, Folder 1705)
    - Scott, Kesho Yvonne, The habit of surviving: black women's strategies for life, 1991; 116513 (Box 36, Folder 1706)
    - Smith, Barbara, ed., Home girls: a black feminist anthology, 1983; 116512 (Box 36, Folder 1707)
    - Wolfe, Tom, The bonfire of the vanities, 1987; 116511 (Box 36, Folder 1708)
  - Subseries L: Media - Video and Audio, 116361
    - Title: [no label], 116509 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1181)
    - Title: Deep Sea Diving At Night With a Camera, 116508 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1183)
      Director: Eder, Elsa
    - Title: Corazon Sangrante, 116507 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1184)
      Director: Cueva, Ximena
    - Title: [untitled], 116506 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1188)
      Director: Codagnone, Alessandro
    - Title: Xochitl Tlayecouani / Flower Warrior, 116505 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1189)
      Director: Tracy, Michael
    - Title: Frankie, 116504 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1190)
      Director: Soffa, Fred
    - Title: Detour, 116503 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1191)
      Duration: 28 minutes
    - Title: Cosmic Sex, 116502 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1193)
      Director: Cheryl, Gail, Aya
    - Title: Emilia Smokebomb Video Shorts: [1.]--Love and Eating Disorder [2.]--A Femme in Butch Clothing [3.]--Germany, 116501 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1195)
      Director: [1.]--Sts [2.]--Real, Emily B. [3.]--Sts
    - Title: He She Pee, 116500 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1196)
      Director: Surkis, A.
    - Title: Switch, 116499 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1197)
    - Title: [1.]--Red Jam Picnic [2.]--Some Egg Blowing, 116498 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1199)
      Director: Kunin, Julia
    - Title: Antigone: Rites of Passion, 116497 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1201)
      Director: Greenfield, Amy
    - Title: Gay Cuba, 116496 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1203)
      Director: de Vries, Sonja
    - Title: [1.]--Magic Cottage [2.]--Nelson Mandela Is Not Ugly, 116495 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1206)
    - Title: La Mascara, 116494 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1207)
      Duration: [30 minutes?]
    - Title: [1.]--It's About Me [2.]--Pixelvision Sex [3.]--Airiana the Human Arrow, 116493 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1208)
      Director: [1-2.]--Real, Emily B. [2.]--Star, Cynthia
    - Title: Senate Media Services Demo Tape, 116492 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1209)
    - Title: Back To My Roots, 116491 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1210)
      Director: RuPaul
    - Title: New British Video, 116490 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1216)
    - Title: Hey There Good Neighbor, 116489 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1218)
    - Title: [1.]--VULVA [2.]--Vers la Dame Jouanne, 116488 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1219)
      Director: [1.]--Thirache, Marcelle [2.]--Burford, Jennifer L.
    - Title: Les Yeup Brouilles, 116487 (Box 76, Folder ID: 143.1224)
      Old number: 5717
      Director: Lauge, Remi
    - Title: In The Spirit of Stonewall: Queers Fighting AIDS, 116486 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1227)
      Old number: 12, 228
      Director: [Wentry] and Donehoo
    - Title: Gym Noir, 116485 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1229)
      Old number: 6331 #2
      Director: Sadomaoistan
    - Title: Paraiso Yucateco, 116484 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1230)
      Director: Avila, Claudia / Cascante, Enrique / Ferrera-Balanquet, Raul / Lugo, Alfredo
    - Title: Lasbisch-TV no. 19 fur Kabellose Dameu, 116483 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1231)
      Director: [1.]--Lein, Mahide [2.]--Lein/Porcheron [3.]--Schleppegrell/Percillier [4.]--Barock, K./Sawyer [5.]--Grunenberg/Sawyer [6.]--Ingenweyen, B. [7.]--Grunenberg/Sawyer [8.]--Vehlow, A. [9.]--Schleppegrell/Percillier [10.]--Sawyer [11.]--Sawyer/Grunenberg
      Distributor: additional credits: [12.]--Biedermann, Chr.
    - Title: Sample Tape - Free Speech TV, 116482 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1232)
    - Title: Straight For The Money: Interviews With Queer Sex Workers, 116481 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1233)
    - Title: Supergay, 116480 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1234)
    - Title: Swoosh, 116479 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1236)
      Director: Malaran, Barbara and Kramer, Lisa
    - Title: Straight For The Money, 116478 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1237)
    - Title: How to Have a Sex Party, 116477 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1462)
      Director: House O'Chicks, Inc.
    - Title: Blending Milk and Water: Sex In The New World, 116476 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1463)
    - Title: Our House: Gays and Lesbians in the Hood, Screened: 1996; 116475 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1464)
      Old number: V14
      Director: Not Channel Zero
    - Title: The Milkmen, 116474 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1465)
      Director: Bruce, John
    - Title: Orphee and Eurydice, Screened: [1995]; 116473 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1466)
      Old number: 6331 #3
      Director: Zermallen, A.
    - Title: Rove, 116472 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1468)
      Director: Patierno, Mary
    - Title: Growing To Darkness, 116471 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1469)
      Director: d'Souza, Kevin
    - Title: It Never Was You, 116470 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1470)
      Director: Siemer, P. and Steger, L.
    - Title: Outta the Blue, 116469 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1471)
    - Title: Safer Play - Safer Sex, Screened: [1992]; 116468 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1482)
      Director: The Naz Project
    - Title: Amami Se Voui or #5, Screened: [1994]; 116467 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1484)
      Director: Curran, Michael
    - Title: The Jaguar and The Giraffe, Screened: [1999]; 116466 (Box 77, Folder ID: 143.1486)
      Director: Firebird Productions
    - Title: Quartier Mozart, Screened: [1992]; 116465 (Box 78, Folder ID: 143.1488)
      Director: Bekolo, Jean-Pierre
    - Title: Jeff Burns: Sag Aftra Aea, Screened: Unknown; 116464 (Box 78, Folder ID: 143.1491)
      Director: Burns, Jeff
    - Title: I Was a Jewish Sex Worker, Screened: [1996]; 116463 (Box 78, Folder ID: 143.1494)
    - Title: Savage Island, Screened: Unkown; 116462 (Box 78, Folder ID: 143.1495)
      Director: Kopp, Gisela
    - Title: Stations of the Cross, Screened: [1993]; 116461 (Box 78, Folder ID: 143.1501)
      Director: Blacklips Performance Cult
    - Title: Mujeria I and II, Screened: [1992]; 116460 (Box 78, Folder ID: 143.1503)
      Director: Osa Hidalgo - de la Rivera
    - Title: Bad Attitude, Screened: Unknown; 116459 (Box 78, Folder ID: 143.1506)
      Director: Mulcaster, Jeff
    - Title: Beautiful Bones, Screened: Unknown; 116458 (Box 78, Folder ID: 143.1507)
    - Title: Say Hello to a Cow's Red Ass, Screened: Unknown; 116457 (Box 78, Folder ID: 143.1508)
    - Title: Lady Fingers, Screened: Unknown; 116456 (Box 78, Folder ID: 143.1514)
      Director: Gonzalez, Rita and Rachel Mayeri
      Duration: 11 minutes
    - Title: Fantasmagoria: sexing the lesbian imaginary, Screened: Unknown; 116455 (Box 78, Folder ID: 143.1519)
      Director: Wolf, Carla, Sandi Sommers, Maureen Badley, Celine Godberson, Anne Golden, A. Vanilla Stitch
    - Title: Speedy Boys, Screened: Unknown; 116454 (Box 78, Folder ID: 143.1520)
      Director: Herbert, James
    - Title: Velvet Mafia Commandoes, Screened: [1999]; 116453 (Box 78, Folder ID: 143.1521)
    - Title: One Night in Heaven, Screened: [1995]; 116452 (Box 78, Folder ID: 143.1522)
      Old number: P95053
    - Title: Sex Flesh in Blood, Screened: Unknown; 116451 (Box 78, Folder ID: 143.1523)
      Director: Lee, Christopher and J. Zapata
    - Title: Dyke TV, Screened: Unknown; 116450 (Box 78, Folder ID: 143.1532)
      Director: Teena, Brandon
    - Title: South African Black Lesbian Stories of Seduction, Screened: [1995]; 116449 (Box 78, Folder ID: 143.1533)
      Old number: 228
    - Title: Italia Delle Regioni 35, Screened: Unknown; 116448 (Box 78, Folder ID: 143.1542)
    - Title: Black Russians, Screened: Uknown; 116447 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1543)
      Director: Uknown
    - Title: MIX, Screened: Unknown; 116446 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1549)
    - Title: Only Enough To Ignite: Some Unpreventable Adventures in Lesbian Flirtation (Preview Trailer), Screened: [1996]; 116445 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1551)
      Director: Gitanjali
    - Title: I am Sorry Dave, Screened: Unknown; 116444 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1554)
    - Title: Heavy Date, Screened: [1992]; 116443 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1555)
      Director: Tri-Larry Production
    - Title: Voices from the Inside: [1.]-- Corpusculaire [2.]-- J'entends le Noir [3.]-- L'Homme Hippocampe, Screened: Unknown; 116442 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1556)
      Director: LaFontaine, Yves
    - Title: Chatter, Screened: Unknown; 116441 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1557)
    - Title: Untitled (For Abramovic, Love Cocteau), Screened: 2000; 116440 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1560)
      Director: Chang, Patty
    - Title: Impaired by Confusion, Screened: [1999]; 116439 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1561)
      Director: [sck]
    - Title: Cutaways and Introductions (2), Screened: Unknown; 116438 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1563)
    - Title: Homoteens (Preview Copy), Screened: [1993]; 116437 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1571)
      Director: Jubela, Joan
    - Title: "Girlfriend" In A Coma (Work in Progress), Screened: [1994]; 116436 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1573)
      Director: Beck, Robert
    - Title: [1.]-- XHistory [2.]-- Queer [3.]-- True Power Club, Screened: Unknown; 116435 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1574)
    - Title: In the Life #30S, Screened: Unknown; 116434 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1575)
      Old number: 30S
    - Title: Miss Boy Bar '95 (Raw Footage), Screened: Unknown; 116433 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1576)
      Old number: #4 80486
    - Title: General Della Rovere, Screened: Unknown; 116432 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1577)
      Director: [Rossellini, Roberto]
    - Title: Cuz It's Boy, Screened: [1994]; 116431 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1578)
    - Title: Scream Queens Promo, Screened: [1997]; 116430 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1579)
      Director: Glamour TV Company
    - Title: [Puzzle Piece], Screened: Unknown; 116429 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1581)
      Director: Bourget, William
    - Title: HOTHEADS, Screened: [1993]; 116428 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1582)
      Director: Livingston, Jennie
    - Title:, Screened: Unknown; 116427 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1583)
    - Title: MiesMovieZine, Screened: Unknown; 116426 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1584)
      Old number: D - 22767
    - Title: B / Side, Screened: [1996]; 116425 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1585)
      Director: Child, Abigail
    - Title: Frankie Goes Downtown, Screened: Unknown; 116424 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1586)
      Old number: K7d v.12.8791
    - Title: Angesichts ihrer fatalen Veranlagung scheidet Lilo Wanders freiwillig aus dem Leben, Screened: [1994]; 116423 (Box 79, Folder ID: 143.1588)
    - Title: La Fruta, Screened: [1991]; 143.1591; 116422 (Box 80, Cassette 143.1591, E-records fales_mss143, E-records 143.1591)
      Old number: MT 02
      Director: Barrero, Roly Chang
      Duration: 3 minutes
    - Title: Michelle Mahrer Show Reel, Screened: [1996]; 116421 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1594)
    - Title: HoMoVISIONES, Screened: Unknown; 116420 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1598)
    - Title: Mix Brasil '99, Screened: 1998; 116419 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1599)
      Old number: 38265 1
    - Title: Encounter at Intergalactic Café, Screened: 1996; 116418 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1606)
      Director: Harriss, Thomas Allen
    - Title: The Wrong Son, Screened: [1993]; 116417 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1608)
      Director: Oliver, Bill
    - Title: Complicated Flesh, Screened: [1994]; 116416 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1611)
      Director: Deustch, Kristina and Cheryl Dunye
      Duration: 60 mintues
    - Title: Since Yesterday, Screened: 1997; 116415 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1613)
      Director: Gretzel, Hanzel
    - Title: 'Way to Go: 5 All Aboard a Bus, Screened: Unknown; 116414 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1614)
      Director: Maryland ITV: Maryland State Department of Education
    - Title: Not Angel But Angels, Screened: [1994]; 116413 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1615)
      Director: Grodecki, Wiktor
    - Title: CenterSeat (Presentation Reel), Screened: Unknown; 116412 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1616)
    - Title: [1.]-- After That It's OK [2.]-- The Queer are Dead, Long Live the Queer, Screened: [1994]; 116411 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1617)
    - Title: [Stumpf], Screened: Unknown; 116410 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1619)
      Director: [Kiki Perrsen]
    - Title: Voices of Life: People Living w/ AIDS, Screened: Unknown; 116409 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1621)
    - Title: Voices of Life: People Living w/ AIDS, Screened: Unknown; 116408 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1622)
      Format:
    - Title: [1.]-- Aquarium [2.]-- Sadistic Self=Portrait [3.]-- Spider Jan.16.91 [4.]-- Inner Sanctum, Screened: Unknown; 116407 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1623)
    - Title: Life and Death on the A-List, Screened: [1996]; 116406 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1624)
      Director: Corcoran, Jay
    - Title: Only Human: HIV-negative gay men in the AIDS epidemic, Screened: 1998; 116405 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1625)
      Director: Mookas, Ioannis
    - Title: Facing AIDS: Stories of Health Care Workers, Screened: Unknown; 116404 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1626)
      Old number: 503
      Director: Bread and Roses Cultural Projects
    - Title: Peer Education Not Fear Education: An AIDS Community Television Presentation, Screened: Unknown; 116403 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1627)
      Director: beer, Tom and Ioannis Mookas
    - Title: The Way of the Wicked, Screened: Unknown; 116402 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1628)
      Director: Vachon, Christine
    - Title: Before Stonewall: The Making of a Gay and Lesbian Communiy, Screened: Unknown; 116401 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1629)
      Director: Schiller, Greta
    - Title: [1.]-- Art Academy [2.]-- Upstairs Inside [3.]-- Desire Drives Her Car, Screened: Unknown; 116400 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1630)
      Director: Maitland-Carter, Kathleen
    - Title: Queerisms, Screened: Unknown; 116399 (Box 80, Folder ID: 143.1632)
    - Title: [1.]-- Couples [2.]-- Love Objects, Screened: [2002]; 116398 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1633)
    - Title: [1.]-- Ophelia and the Cat Lady [2.]-- Phases of the Moon [3.]-- Oblivion [4.]-- Gloria in the Glass [5.]-- A Persian Rug, Screened: [2002]; 116397 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1634)
    - Title: [1.]-- Endymion [2.]-- The Heavens [3.]-- Earth [4.]-- Joe's Maison, Screened: [2002]; 116396 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1635)
      Director: [1.]-- Glin, Joseph [2, 3, 4]-- Chomont, Tom
    - Title: [1.]-- Minor Revisions [2.]-- Razor Head, Screened: [2002]; 116395 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1636)
    - Title: A Faustian Knot, Screened: [2002]; 116394 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1637)
      Director: Chomont, Tom and Clark Coleman
    - Title: The Dog Diary, Screened: [2002]; 116393 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1638)
    - Title: Age 12: Love With a Little L, Screened: [1990]; 116392 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1639)
    - Title: Dyke Match Comp. Tape (Parts I, II, III, IV), Screened: Unknown; 116391 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1641)
      Director: Schaffner, Sue
    - Title: Tomboy, Screened: [1994]; 116390 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1642)
      Old number: 182
      Director: Logsdon, Dawn
    - Title: Unknown, Screened: [6.28.1994]; 116389 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1650)
      Format: S-VHS
    - Title: Without Make-up You Haven't Got a Prayer, Screened: Unknown; 116388 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1654)
      Director: Nurudin, Azian
    - Title: Coupilatia, Screened: Unknown; 116387 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1657)
    - Title: You: A Tribute to Mothers, Screened: Unknown; 116386 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1658)
      Director: Sotoodeh, Kayvan
    - Title: 1998 My Queer Career: Australian and New Zealand Queer Shorts Competition, Screened: Unknown; 116385 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1665)
      Director: Queer Screen
    - Title: Uh… (Taylor), Screened: Unknown; 116384 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1667)
      Director: Goldberg, Gary
    - Title: Mies Movie Zine, Screened: Unknown; 116383 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1669)
      Old number: 5338 135
    - Title: If You Don't Like It, Don't Call, Screened: Unknown; 116382 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1679)
    - Title: Fanci's Persuasion, Screened: Unknown; 116381 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1680)
      Director: [Herman-Wurmfeld, Charles]
    - Title: Carmelo, Screened: [1995]; 116380 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1683)
      Director: Oerli, Christoph
    - Title: Spiritual Warfare: The G.H.O.S.T. Campaign, Screened: Unknown; 116379 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1684)
      Director: Harlot, Scarlet
    - Title: Teresinha Remix, Screened: Unknown; 116378 (Box 81, Folder ID: 143.1685)
    - Title: [1.]-- Wargasm [2.]-- Belvobnida, Screened: Unknown; 116377 (Box 82, Folder ID: 143.1692)
      Director: Turcios, Karla
    - Title: HHHHHi, Screened: Unknown; 116376 (Box 82, Folder ID: 143.1696)
      Director: Jaffrennou, Julie
    - Title: Roy Cohn/Jack Smith, Screened: Unknown; 116375 (Box 82, Folder ID: 143.1701)
      Director: [unknown]
    - Title: [1.]-- 1976 [2.]-- Marie Claire 1938 [3.]-- La femme et la vie du Poyer [4.]-- Un temoignage [5.]-- Interruption degrossesse d'esprit [6.]-- Installation Super 8, fenetre etage, Screened: Unknown; 116374 (Box 82, Folder ID: 143.1709)
      Director: Axpe, Ana
    - Title: On Our Way to Hollywood, Screened: Unknown; 116373 (Box 82, Folder ID: 143.1712)
      Director: Keegan-Sommers, James
    - Title: Untitled (Going Out of My Head), Screened: [1994]; 116372 (Box 82, Folder ID: 143.1715)
      Director: Monforte, Ivan
    - Title: Disappearing Act, Screened: Unknown; 116371 (Box 82, Folder ID: 143.1719)
      Director: DreamKeeper Productions
    - Title: Batiman and Robin, Screened: Unknown; 116370 (Box 82, Folder ID: 143.1724)
      Director: Branco, Ivo
    - Title: I.K.U. VJ Trailer E-Male CG, Screened: Unknown; 116369 (Box 82, Folder ID: 143.1728)
      Director: Cheang, Shu Lea
    - Title: Cinematon: Personnalites du Cinema Francais, Screened: Unknown; 116368 (Box 82, Folder ID: 143.1730)